(Raj:)Mouthwash, lotion, body wash,
shampoo and conditioner...
(Raj:)...together in one tiny bottle.
(Raj:)I love Las Vegas.
Hey, Howard,
can I borrow some aftershave?
(Howard:)Black case, top compartment.
That's a lot of cologne.
HOWARD:
First row are your musks.
Second is woods, leathers and botanicals.
(Howard:)Third is assorted pheromones.
Tread lightly.
(Raj(finding a large quantity of condoms):)That's the spirit, Howard.
(Raj(finding a large quantity of condoms):)Yes, we can.
(Leonard:)Come on, let's go.
(Howard:)You guys go ahead.
I just have to finish up an e-mail.
(Leonard:)That's not an e-mail,
that's Leslie's Facebook page.
(Howard:)Okay, fine.
I'm checking her Facebook page.
(Howard:)Look at her status update.
(Howard:)She's saying she dumped me.
People need to know I dumped her.